哈罗
Hello!
咦 这是什么？
What's this?
啊 对了 是那个女生的电话
Oh, right! It's that girl's phone number.
在这里 一个粉辣的女生
There it is. Just a phone number...
给我的电话
...a really hot girl gave me.
也没什么 只是她家的电话…
No big deal. I mean, it is her home phone number but...
哇
Whoa!
真是的 差点就掉了
Whoops! Heh. Almost lost this baby!
可爱的亚曼达把电话给我 我却掉了
The lovely Amanda gives me her number, and I go and drop it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 瑞秋   - 嗯？
- Rachel?     - Yeah?
- 你的生日是几号？ - 5月5号 做什么？
- When's your birthday?     - May 5th. Why?
我只是在记大家的生日
I'm making a list of birthdays.
- 我是12月…   - 随便
- Mine's December...     - Yeah, whatever.
她真漂亮
Oh! She's pretty!
好漂亮 真… 好… 真漂亮
Pretty, uh, pretty girl. The pretty... She's pretty.
去约她嘛
- Go ask her out.     - Ha, ha.
- 有什么大不了的？ - 我搞不好会死
- What's the worst that could happen?     - I could die.
一个人的确很难熬
Yeah, it's tough being single.
所以我很高兴我认识了亚曼达
That's why I'm so glad I found Amanda.
罗斯 你们只出去过一次
Ross, you guys went out once.
你们带小孩去游乐城 你连亲都没亲她
You took your kids to Chuck E. Cheese, and you didn't even kiss her.
我会泄露秘密
I tell people secrets.
好让别人喜欢我
It makes them like me.
嘿
Hey.
菲比
Phoebe.
你生病了 别唱了 回家上床休息吧
You're sick. You shouldn't play. Go home.
但是我失业了
But I'm unemployed.
我只剩下音乐
My music is all I really have now.
音乐和自己做鞋子 很美吧？
Well, music and making my own shoes. Pretty, huh?
好 我去
All right, I'll do it.
我去接受枪毙
I'll go get shot down.
有什么建议？
Any advice?
展现你的本色
Just be yourself...
但是不要太过火
...but not too much.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
加油
Good luck!
请用祝祷的
Wish it!
你好 我坐在那里…
Hi. I was just sitting over there and...
我是钱德 我有说吗？
Uh, my name's Chandler. Did I say that?
没有 你好 我是凯西
No, you didn't. Hi, I'm Kathy.
- 凯子的凯吗？- 没错
- Kathy with a K or a C?     - With OK.
嘿
Hey!
你还真会搭讪
Wow, you are really good at this!
别这么说 我很尴尬
I'm out on a limb here!
你说得对 我道歉
I'm sorry. You're right.
但是我跟别人有约
But I should tell you I'm waiting for a date.
他来了
And there he is now!
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey!     - Hey!
- Hey! Hey!     - Hey!
你们已经认识了
- I see you guys already met.     - Yeah.
是啊 我正在示范
I was trying to demonstrate...
如何把我那很大的脚
...how I could get my very large feet...
塞进我那更大的嘴里
...into my even bigger mouth.
我就说吧
Didn't I tell you?
他最爱现了
Always showing off.
首先我要说 我感冒了
Before I start, I want to say that I have a cold.
要是我唱到一半打喷嚏 那不是故意的
So if I sneeze during a song, it's not on purpose.
除了《胡椒人》的最后一句
Oh! Except the last verse of "Pepper People."
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
[SINGING IN CONGESTED VOICE] Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你吃什么？
What are they feeding you?
这声音不赖喔
This chick sounds good.
臭臭猫 臭臭…
Smelly cat
阿甘 乖 拿杯威士忌来
Gunther, be a good little boy and bring me a whiskey.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
想不到半夜2点半 还要抢遥控器
At 2:30 a.m., I didn't expect to fight over the remote.
对不起 我想看厄尼柯瓦克斯的重播
Sorry, there's this Ernie Kovacs thing I wanted to watch.
我也是要看那个
That's why I got up too.
不会吧？我爱死他了
You're kidding? I love him!
下午很抱歉 要是知道你们… 我也不会…
Sorry about this afternoon. If I'd known, I wouldn't have...
道什么歉
Oh, please. Heh.
乔伊说你们是在表演课认识的
Joey tells me you two met in acting class.
对 我们两个一组 乔伊选了三场戏
We were partners. Joey picked three scenes for us.
- 三场都是亲热戏   - 哈哈
- All of them had us making out.     - Ha-ha-ha.
太好了 他原先都逼我跟他练
That's good, because he used to make me rehearse with him.
- 噢   - 开始了吗？
- Oh, oh, oh!     - Is it on?
还没 但是这个伸缩扫把很棒
No, but this wonder broom is amazing!
嘿
Hey!
就是它
Oh, my God!
开始了
Oh! It's on!
小不点 过来
Here we go, little fella.
那鸭子呢？
What about the duck?
- 鸭子会游泳   - 也对
- The duck can swim.     - Of course.
烂泥巴鞋
My sticky shoes
沾满烂泥巴的鞋
My sticky, sticky shoes
你为什么黏着我不放
Why you stick on me,
宝贝？
Baby?
谢谢你的灯光
Thanks for the lights, honey.
太精彩了
Way to go!
你的声音好有磁性
Your cold makes you sound great.
好好玩 我真是太性戚了
It's fun. God, I love how sexy I am!
凯西 该走了 我们要去买仓鼠
Kath, we should get going. We're going to buy hamsters.
我喜欢仓鼠
Aw. I love them.
不是那样的 我在替一个医疗研究员工作
No, it's not like that. I work for a medical researcher.
- 去玩吧   - 好的
- Have fun.     - Okay.
医学界总算也在救助
It's nice that the medical community...
生病的仓鼠了
...is trying to help sick hamsters.
- 我喜欢凯西   - 是的么？
- You know, I like Kathy.     - Yeah?
我也是 她好酷 好漂亮
Me too! She's so cool and pretty.
是啊 她…
She is.
她既聪明又风趣
She's smart and funny.
我们昨晚聊了一整夜 她聊到一些…
We were up all last night talking. She said the funniest thing about...
怎样？
What?
你爱她
You love her.
我没有
No, I don't.
你有 钱德爱凯西
Yes, you do. Chandler loves Kathy.
- 菲比 饶了他吧   - 谢了 罗斯
- Come on, just lay off him.     - Thank you.
他现在有点敏感 因为他恋爱了
He's a little sensitive right now because he's so in love!
好吧
All right.
凯西
Ooh, Kathy!
我爱你
Kathy, I love you!
我得写一些悲情的歌 来配合我的新哭腔
I need to write some depressing stuff for my new bluesy voice.
但是我没有悲惨的遭遇
But nothing sad has ever happened to me.
你妈自杀的事呢？
How about your mom dying?
或是你14岁时流落街头？
Or living on the streets when you were 14?
我可以写头发翘起来那次
I could write about when my hair did that woo-hoo thing.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我晚上要去亚曼达家
I'm going over to Amanda's tonight.
- 瑞秋不在   - 哦
- Rachel's not here.     - Oh.
你跟她进展如何？
How's it going with her?
很棒 搞不好今晚就有机会
Great, actually. I'm thinking tonight may be the night.
两个孩子会一起玩 等他们睡了
The kids will play together, and when they're asleep...
亚曼达和我再开一瓶酒
...Amanda and I break open a bottle of wine...
我们自己来玩
...do a little playing ourselves.
嗨 这是贾许
Hi, guys! This is Josh.
贾许 她们是我的朋友
Josh, these are my friends.
那是罗斯
And that's Ross.
- 贾许   - 你好
- Hi, Josh.     - Hi.
你打过校队？
You played in college?
现在还是 明年我想进大学
Aw, I still do. Next year, I hope to make varsity.
罗斯 你高中不是踢过足球？
Didn't you play soccer in high school?
不对 你只是用电脑帮他们排赛程表
No, wait. You organized their game schedules on your Commodore 64.
不早了 我还有球赛 先闪了
It's getting late. I got to get to the game, so I'll... head.
我会想你的
I'll miss you.
爽
Dope!
- 很可爱嘛   - 非常可爱
Wow! Cute one.
我知道 他很棒吧？
- Very cute.     - I know. Isn't he great?
总算来了一段有趣的恋情
So nice to finally be in a fun relationship, you know?
他一点也不无聊
There's nothing boring about him.
我敢赌他一定没进过博物馆
I bet he's never set foot in a museum.
也许他快要有机会了
Maybe he'll get to go soon.
像校外教学什么的
Like on a class trip or something.
你们知道他还有哪里好？
You know what else is great about him?
该怎么形容
Ugh, what's the word for an adult...
房间里没有恐龙玩具的男人？
...who has no dinosaur toys in their bedroom?
哦…
Oh...
什么意思？
What was that?
摩妮卡知道
Monica knows.
那是罗斯发明来唬爸妈的
It's this dumb thing Ross made up to fool our parents.
其实就是比中指的意思
It's a way of giving the finger without actually giving it.
你发明这个手势让我哭了
I cried the night you made that up.
我第一次明白我比我哥酷
It was the first time I realized I was cooler than my big brother.
我要去准备…
I'm going to go get ready...
赴今晚的约了
...for my date tonight...
先闪了
...so I'll just head.
我也该走了 1小时后要上台
I should go too. I'm playing in one hour.
嘿…
Hey...
你们应该来听
You guys should come hear me. Ooh!
来听
Hear me. Ooh!
烂泥巴鞋…
My sticky shoes
哦
Ew! Ew!
我的性感破锣嗓没了
I lost my sexy phlegm!
- 嗨   - 嗨 班
- Hi.     - Hi. Hi, Ben.
- 你好性感   - 谢谢
- You look great!     - Thanks.
汤米
Hey, Tommy!
我好高兴你今晚能来
I'm so glad you could come tonight.
不 这是我的荣幸
Oh, no. It's my pleasure.
我的手机号码在餐台上
My cell phone number is on the counter.
冰箱里的东西自己拿
Help yourself to the fridge.
真的很谢谢你
I appreciate this. I've been trying to date...
我想约这个男的想了好久
...this guy for a month.
我…
I...
能不能请你…
Uh, I'd appreciate it if you'd drink your wine...
等孩子睡了再喝酒
...after the kids are asleep.
哦…
Oh, uh...
谢谢你 希望改天我也能帮你
Thanks for this. I hope I can do the same for you sometime.
谁想打长途电话？
Who wants to make some long     -distance calls?
凯西 凯西 喂
Kathy! Kathy!
凯西 凯西
Hi, Kathy! Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
凯西 凯西
Fetch! Fetch it!
凯西 凯西 凯西
Kathy! Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
钱德 你怎么在这里？
Hey. Chandler, what are you doing here?
我只是来打个招呼
I just wanted to say, "hey!"
- 嘿   - 好
- Hey!     - Okay.
你说得太严重了吧
You're making it sound worse than it was.
她的男伴给了我10块钱 当小费
Her date tipped me $10!
菲比 你干什么？
What are you doing?
我想恢复性感 所以我想感冒
I want to be sexy again, so I'm trying to catch a cold.
应该很容易 威冒很常见
Should be easy. They're pretty common.
你会得肺炎
You'll catch pneumonia!
你们说得对 我爱上了乔伊的女朋友
You were right. I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
- 什么？- 真的吗？
- What?     - Are you serious?
怎么可能？你们根本不熟
How's that possible? You barely know her.
我不晓得 我就是…
I don't know. I just...
我就是无法忘掉她
I can't get her out of my head.
我很糟糕 非常非常糟…
I'm a very bad person. I'm a very, very bad person.
我是个烂人
I'm a horrible person.
"才不是呢 我们还是爱你"
"No, you're not. We still love you, Chandler!"
我染上你的感冒了
Phoebe, I think I caught your cold.
是偷走才对
You mean you stole it!
打喷嚏不要捂嘴巴
Don't cover your mouth when you do that!
嘿
Hey.
我们正在说你
We were just talking about you.
真的？
Really?
对 就是你喝醉
The time you got drunk and fell asleep...
头泡在马桶里睡着那次
...with your head in the toilet.
泡得刚刚好
Right in there!
99… 100
Ninety nine...
我来捉你们了
...a hundred. Ready or not, here I come!
我再解释一次规则
Let's go over the concept one more time.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey!     - Hey!
小家伙们 晚上要不要跟我们吃饭？
You want to get some dinner with me and Kathy tonight?
我已经吃饱了
Oh, um... You know what? I already ate.
- 才4点半   - 我星期一吃得很饱
- It's 4:30.     - I had a big meal on Monday.
可以撑一整个礼拜
So that'll get me straight through the week.
好 我知道是怎么回事
I see what's going on here.
- 你知道？ - 是的
- You do?     - Yeah.
对 你不喜欢凯西
You don't like Kathy.
被你猜对了
You got me.
我们交往至今 你一直在躲她
You've been avoiding her since we started dating.
我曾经努力去喜欢珍妮丝
I made an effort to like Janice.
现在该你试着去喜欢凯西 陪我们去吃饭了 对吧？
Now you make an effort to like Kathy by going out with us. Right?
- 对 没错   - 很好 而且我请客
- Yeah, right.     - Good. And hey, my treat.
不过你不吃 对吧？
Because you're not eating, right?
对
Right.
罗斯不在
Ross isn't here.
放手
Oh. Stop it!
那我们派对上见
I'll see you at the party?
啤酒免费喝到饱
Beer's fear, man!
耶
Yeah!
我一定会嫁给他
I am so going to marry that guy.
- 呃   - 怎么了？
- Ugh!     - What?
我觉得他偷我的钱
I think he's stealing from me.
为什么？
Why?
因为他真的偷我的钱
Because he's stealing from me!
- 是我   - 嗨
- Hi, it's me.     - Hi.
还有热汤
And soup.
贾许穿你的皮衣看起来好帅
I saw Josh. He looked yummy in your leather jacket.
来 我不吃鸡 所以只有汤
I don't eat chicken, so it's just noodle soup.
熬汤时又没放鸡 跟水没两样
There's no chicken in the broth, so it's really noodle water.
- 谢谢你   - 不客气
- Thank you so much.     - Sure.
你拿那个干嘛？
What are you doing?
我要你的细菌 我想再感冒
I need your germs. I want my cold back.
我怀念我的性感嗓音
I miss my sexy voice.
对不起
Sorry, Phoebe.
没关系
It's okay.
汤好喝吗？
- How's the soup?     - Mm.
那个女生的内衣都露出来了
Oh! Check it out! You can see that girl's underwear.
她很棒吧？
- Is she great, or what?     - Ha, ha.
你觉得她如何？
Huh? What do you think?
她不是我的型
She's not really my type.
不是你的型？大美女耶
Not your type? She's gorgeous.
因为她穿网袜
You know what it is? The fishnet stockings.
看到女生穿网袜 我就想到…
Whenever I see a girl in those, it reminds me of...
我爸穿网袜的样子
...my father in fishnet stockings.
好吧 我有点了解你为何单身了
Understanding a little more of why you're single.
我有个很漂亮的朋友 我们可以一起约会
I have a friend you'd like. We could double date.
不必了
No, thanks.
好 我也有几个丑朋友没有对象
I've got some ugly friends who are available too.
我去叫酒
I'm going to grab a beer.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
- 你什么意思？- 什么？
- What was that?     - What?
凯西在示好 你却掉头就走 我们不是说好了？
Kathy's being really nice and you walked away.
你要我怎样？
What do you want from me?
我要你喜欢她
I want you to like her.
要是太难了 你起码可以装一下
If that's too damn difficult, then at least you could pretend.
我正在装啊
I am pretending.
那就再像一点
Then do it better.
好 不如我去说我很喜欢她
What do you say, I go tell her how much I like her?
我可以说我一直在想她
I could tell her I've been thinking of her.
认识之后我就一直想着她
I haven't stopped thinking of her since we met.
我无可救药 简直想撕裂自己的爱着她
I'm so over the top, want to slit my own throat...
每一天的每一分每一秒
...in love with her, that every minute...
我都在怨恨为何是你先认识她
...I can't believe my own damn bad luck that you met her first!
很不错
That's pretty good.
但是别那么夸张
But you might want to tone it down a little.
是亚曼达载我来的
Hey. Uh, Amanda just dropped me off.
我就喜欢她这一点
That's one of the things I love about her.
成年人可以开车
She's old enough to drive.
你晚上不去找爸妈了？
You're not going to Mom and Dad's tonight?
不了 对不起
No. Sorry.
亚曼达呢？
Where's Amanda?
瑞秋 帮我拿咳嗽药水
Get me some cough drops.
我在想 你可以带她去你的旧房间
I'm thinking you could bring her...
然后不上床
...and go to your old room and not make out.
罗斯 咳嗽药水
Cough drop, please?
至少她跟我出去
At least she's not going out with me...
不是为了看限制级电影
...to get into R-rated movies.
你怎么不娶她算了？
Why don't you marry her?
我忘了 你不行 她不是同性恋
Wait, you can't! I forgot. She's not a lesbian.
亚曼达和我…
Amanda and I...
什么都不是
You have nothing!
你们根本没在约会 你是她的保姆
You're not even going out! You're her babysitter.
你在做小女生做的事
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
真可悲啊
Oh, that is so sad.
你笑什么 你男朋友还不是爱喝酒
What are you laughing at, Miss My keg ucking boyfriend...
又偷钱
... is stealing from me?
他偷了几块钱又怎样
So he stole a few bucks. Big deal!
他有买东西给我
He got me something with it.
那是我的
That's mine!
你们两个成熟一点好吗？
Would you both please start acting like adults?
把咳嗽药水拿给我
And give me my cough drops!
- 好   - 对不起
- Fine.     - Sorry.
- 拿去   - 谢谢
- Here.     - Thank you.
至少我还赚了10块钱
At least I made $10 in my relationship.
你…
You know...
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
在大街上游行
Parading down the street
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
留下小脚印
Leaving little treats
用这种声音唱还能听吗？
Does it even work without my sexy voice?
我喜欢
I like it.
- 阿甘 亲我   - 什么？
- Gunther, kiss me.     - What?
副警长 快想办法
Do it, Deputy! Do something!
嘿
Hey!
我们没有要睡 但是小声点
We aren't exactly sleeping in here, but do you mind?
我可以睡你的沙发吗？
Can I sleep on your couch?
我还在等
And I'm still waiting
我的纸黏土人
For my papier mâché man
谢谢各位
Thank you, my babies.
- 瑞秋   - 怎样？
- Rachel?     - Yeah?
我不知道你有没有听说 我和菲比的事
Did you hear what happened between me and Phoebe?
没有
- No.- We kissed.
我们接吻了 不是我主动的 但我也没阻止
I didn't initiate it, but I also didn't stop it.
我一直觉得很内疚
I've been feeling guilty.
好
Okay
所以…
So, um...
我们没事吧？
...are we cool?
好
Okay.
我就知道你会谅解
I knew you would understand.